[OCEAN WAVES]
♪♪♪
♪ TWO AUGUSTS AGO ♪
♪ I TOLD THE TRUTH, OH, BUT YOU
DIDN'T LIKE IT, YOU WENT HOME ♪
♪ YOU'RE IN YOUR BENZ,
I'M BY THE GATE ♪
♪♪♪
♪ NOW YOU GO ALONE ♪
♪ CHARM ALL THE PEOPLE YOU TRAIN
FOR, YOU MEAN WELL BUT AIM LOW ♪
♪ AND I'LL MAKE IT KNOWN LIKE
I'M GETTING PAID
[CHOIR VOCALIZING] ♪
♪ THAT'S JUST THE WAY
LIFE GOES ♪
♪ I LIKE TO SLAM DOORS CLOSED ♪
♪ TRUST ME, I KNOW IT'S ALWAYS
ABOUT ME ♪
♪ I LOVE YOU, I'M SORRY ♪
♪ TWO SUMMERS FROM NOW ♪
♪ WE'LL HAVE BEEN TALKING ♪
♪ BUT NOT ALL THAT OFTEN,
WE'RE COOL NOW ♪
♪ I'LL BE ON A BOAT ♪
♪ YOU'RE ON A PLANE ♪
♪ GOING SOMEWHERE, SAME ♪
♪ AND I'LL HAVE A DRINK ♪
♪ WISTFULLY LEAN OUT MY
WINDOW AND WATCH THE SUN SET
ON THE LAKE ♪
♪ I MIGHT NOT FEEL REAL ♪
♪ BUT IT'S OKAY, MM ♪
♪ 'CAUSE THAT'S JUST
THE WAY LIFE GOES ♪
♪ I PUSH MY LUCK, IT SHOWS ♪
♪ THANKFUL YOU DON'T SEND
SOMEONE TO KILL ME
[CHOIR VOCALIZING] ♪
[DOOR OPENS] [ECHO]
[FOOTSTEPS]
- OH SHIT THAT WAS TONIGHT.
♪♪♪
[INTENCE MUSIC]
[AUDIO FEEDBACK]
♪ I LOVE YOU, I'M SORRY ♪
♪ YOU WERE THE BEST BUT
YOU WERE THE WORST
[CHOIR VOCALIZING] ♪
♪ AS SICK AS IT SOUNDS,
I LOVED YOU FIRST ♪
♪ I WAS A DICK,
IT IS WHAT IT IS ♪
♪ A HABIT TO KICK,
(THE AGE- OLD CURSE) ♪
♪ I TEND TO LAUGH
WHENEVER I'M SAD ♪
♪ I STARE AT THE CRASH,
(IT ACTUALLY WORKS) ♪
♪ MAKING AMENDS,
THIS SHIT NEVER ENDS ♪
♪ I'M WRONG AGAIN, WRONG AGAIN ♪
♪ THE WAY LIFE GOES
[CHOIR VOCALIZING] ♪
♪ JOYRIDING DOWN OUR ROAD ♪
♪ LAY ON THE HORN TO
PROVE THAT IT HAUNTS ME
(I'M WRONG AGAIN, WRONG AGAIN) ♪
♪ I LOVE YOU, I'M SORRY ♪
♪ THE WAY LIFE GOES
(YOU WERE THE BEST BUT
YOU WERE THE WORST) ♪
♪ I WANNA SPEAK IN CODE
(AS SICK AS IT SOUNDS,
I LOVED YOU FIRST) ♪
♪ HOPE THAT I DON'T, WON'T MAKE
IT ABOUT ME (A HABIT TO KICK,
THE AGE-OLD CURSE) ♪
♪♪♪
[CHOIR VOCALIZING]
♪ I LOVE YOU, I'M SORRY ♪
[OCEAN WAVES]
[INDISTINCT CHATTING]
[SCREEMING]
[SCREEMING VOICE]
[INDISTINCT CHATTING]